[Music]
the pandemic has posed some serious
challenges in the indian i.t industries
and to help them navigate through these
turbulent times we bring you india risk
practitioners a special segment as a
part of india risk management awards the
corona virus pandemic is a complex
multifaceted crisis has resulted in
giving rise to various risks and
highlighted the importance of risk
management for the indian i.t industries
in india
we need to now uh
focus uh not just on crisis management
and resilience but being
proactive to look at known and unknown
risks which may come in the future so
building risk management into the
organizations
fabric of strategy design development
and performance is is very key uh and
therefore
it's not just risk managers but every
business manager who needs to
talk the language of risk along with the
business plans and the strategy that
they are rolling out today
along with risks which some sometimes
people tend to think is a negative word
comes a whole host of opportunities so
therefore it's very imperative that
business managers also look at address
risks and look at okay how do i convert
this into an opportunity which may help
us to maybe get into a completely new
line of business for all you know
well to nominate your organization for
the india risk management awards visit
the below link
[Music]